<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Phuket Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="fun_tab">Fun</string>
    <string name="food_tab">Food</string>
    <string name="travel_tab">Travel</string>
    <string name="hotels_tab">Hotels</string>
    <string name="todo1_name">Phuket Sail Tours</string>
    <string name="low_priced_food">฿ - ฿฿</string>
    <string name="medium_priced_food">฿฿ - ฿฿฿</string>
    <string name="high_priced_food">฿฿฿ - ฿฿฿฿</string>
    <string name="very_high_priced_food">฿฿฿฿</string>
    <string name="baht">฿</string>
    <string name="dollar">$</string>
    <string name="unknown_priced_food">\?</string>
    <string name="todo1_desc">Come aboard with us and see the best scenery in the world. Beautiful limestone formations rising straight up out of the sea... and better still, going ashore to explore the hidden lagoons (hongs), caves, and the haunted pirate lair (true, Captain Mark has seen and heard the ghost, but is waiting on directions to the treasure).</string>
    <string name="todo1_url">http://www.phuketsailtours.com/tour_koh_panak.htm</string>
    <string name="todo2_name">Phuket Snorkelling by Offspray Leisure</string>
    <string name="todo2_desc">Phi Phi Daytrips: Spectacular limestone cliffs, emerald tinted lagoons, secluded coves and Phi Phi’s vast array of coral reefs and marine life await our Guests..... We are looking forward to having you aboard!</string>
    <string name="todo2_url">http://www.phuket-snorkeling.com/</string>
    <string name="todo3_name">Sildaon Spa Phuket</string>
    <string name="todo3_desc">Siladon Spa Phuket is a beautiful hillside resort style villa, with a nice garden and pool, and beautiful views of Patong Bay. You can indulge yourself and forget the world for a few hours with a relaxing luxury spa experience.. Price is for Sildaon Bliss + 4 Hands massage</string>
    <string name="todo3_url">http://www.siladonspaphuket.com</string>
    <string name="todo4_name">Healthland Massage Patong</string>
    <string name="todo4_desc">Specialising in traditional Thai massage, we offer all types massages as well as manicure, pedicure, foot and body scrubs, waxing and other health and beauty services.</string>
    <string name="todo_url">http://www.healthlandmassage.com/</string>
    <string name="todo5_name">So Thai Spa</string>
    <string name="todo5_desc">You are invited to enjoy indulgent pampering, combined with relaxation for your body and your mind, and served to you in our tastefully decorated day spa in Phuket (Patong). Price is for 2 hour 4 hands massage</string>
    <string name="todo5_url">http://www.sothaispaphuket.com/</string>
    <string name="todo6_name">Phuket Trickeye Museum</string>
    <string name="todo6_desc">Trickeye museum is an interactive museum with a concept that simulates your creativity and imagination by TROMPEL\'OEIL technique through your vision. The time has come when you can enter the picture, which you used to only watch and become a part of the picture yourself!</string>
    <string name="todo6_url">http://www.phukettrickeyemuseum.com/</string>
    <string name="todo7_name">Kata Thai Cooking Class</string>
    <string name="todo7_desc">Thai cooking school at Kata Beach in Phuket. Daily classes with 3 different dishes incl. a market tour.</string>
    <string name="todo7_url">https://katathaicooking.com/</string>
    <string name="todo8_name">Phuket Thai Cookery School</string>
    <string name="todo8_desc">Phuket Thai Cookery School is definitely the one and only place in phuket island that offers you a haven of peace and serenity away from hustle of the city. Nestled in a prestine beach paradise on Siray beach, Phuket Thai Cookery School allows you comfort and serenity while cooking favorite Thai dishes and enjoying your home made delicious meal.</string>
    <string name="todo8_url">http://www.phuketthaicookery.com/locations/</string>
    <string name="todo9_name">Sunday Walking Street Market (Lard Yai)</string>
    <string name="todo9_desc">The selection of high quality merchandise at an absolute bargain made this a treasure trove of its own. Don’t make the same mistake we did thinking we find these items elsewhere...</string>
    <string name="todo9_url">http://www.google.com/</string>
    <string name="food1_name">La Dolce Vita</string>
    <string name="food1_desc">Went here last night after reading the reviews ordered spag bol (my fave) the pasta was amazing so fresh and not over cooked service was brilliant so gutted I didn\'t get the lamb chops somebody next to me did and they looked amazing!!</string>
    <string name="food1_url">https://www.nirvanaphuket.com/</string>
    <string name="food2_name">Sam\'s Steaks and Grill</string>
    <string name="food2_desc">I must say the restaurant has a good atmosphere, and a good variety of wines. Bread and avocado crab salad were fresh and tasty. Lobster soup was salty but still edible.</string>
    <string name="food2_url">http://www.phuket.holiday-inn.com/sams-steakhouse.htm</string>
    <string name="food3_name">ICC Indian Curry Club</string>
    <string name="food3_desc">A must visit in Patong. Centrally located near the Bangla road. The food was delicious, one of the best Indian meals I have ever had. The customer service, presentation and attention to detail was spot on. Would definitely return to this restaurant.</string>
    <string name="food3_url">http://www.indiancurryclubphuket.com/</string>
    <string name="food4_name">Vista</string>
    <string name="food4_desc">Take a detour through Italy for pizza and pasta, or try Vista’s version of an all-time favorite, fish and chips, on a stopover in the UK. You can also share a fondue with family and friends – choose between the rich, cheesy French version or its lighter Asian counterpart.</string>
    <string name="food4_url">http://www.avista-hideaway-phuket-patong.com/restaurants-bars/vista/</string>
    <string name="food5_name">i-Kroon Cafe</string>
    <string name="food5_desc">Cozy, organised, clean and amazingly fresh and tasty food... Highly recommended if you are looking for good food with affordable price!. If you are a bit tired of traditional Thai taste during your trip and you are looking for a rest... you must visit this...</string>
    <string name="food5_url">http://ikrooncafe.restaurantwebexperts.com/</string>
    <string name="food6_name">La Gritta</string>
    <string name="food6_desc">La Gritta features an elegant design and furnishings, as well as a sumptuous contemporary menu. La Gritta at Amari Phuket offers two distinct sections La Gritta Restaurant and La Gritta Bar, with both indoor and outdoor areas, for a combined seating capacity of 100.</string>
    <string name="food6_url">http://www.lagritta.com/</string>
    <string name="food7_name">Halfway Inn</string>
    <string name="food7_desc">The Halfway Inn is a great place to eat or to just have a drink. Dave, Nan and all the staff are so hospitable and make you feel so welcome.The food prepared by Nan is sensational and it was a pleasure to have a great meal and a few drinks on numerous occasions.</string>
    <string name="food7_url">http://halfwayinn.restaurantwebexperts.com/</string>
    <string name="food8_name">Maru Korean Restaurant</string>
    <string name="food8_desc">The ox noodle soup was average, chewy meat, no flavor to the soup. They serve 5 side dishes including kimchi and a salad which had a few grains of rice in it that didn’t belong there!</string>
    <string name="food8_url">https://www.tripadvisor.com.au/Restaurant_Review-g297930-d6479045-Reviews-Maru_Korean_Restaurant-Patong_Kathu_Phuket.html</string>
    <string name="trav1_name">Phuket International Airport (HKT)</string>
    <string name="trav1_desc">Phuket International Airport is the second busiest airport in Thailand. Millions of passengers each year visit Phuket to enjoy a wide range of tourist services, natural beauty of the world famous Phuket beaches and fascinating tourist attractions.</string>
    <string name="trav1_url">https://www.phuketairportonline.com/</string>
    <string name="trav2_name">Tuk Tuks</string>
    <string name="trav2_desc">Taxis and Tuk Tuks in Phuket are one of the more convenient methods of getting around the island, giving you private transport directly to your destination. While they are more expensive than buses and motorbike taxis, they are much faster than the former and much more comfortable than the latter.</string>
    <string name="trav2_url">http://www.phuket.com/phuket-magazine/taxis-and-tuk-tuks.htm</string>
    <string name="trav3_name">Taxis and GrabTaxi App</string>
    <string name="trav3_desc">For transfer from the airport, there\'s only one authorized \"limousine\" service that has fixed fares. Expect to pay 100-200 Baht for a shared minibus or up to 500 baht for a private taxi, depending on your destination.</string>
    <string name="trav3_url">http://www.phuket.com/phuket-magazine/taxis-and-tuk-tuks.htm</string>
    <string name="trav4_name">Song Taew</string>
    <string name="trav4_desc">Phuket Local Beach Bus offers you many different routes to take you wherever you need to go, whether it’s Patong, Kata, Karon or Rawai. It is far from the fastest or most luxurious way to travel, but it’s the cheapest method of getting from Phuket Town to all the beaches.</string>
    <string name="trav4_url">http://www.phuket.com/phuket-magazine/phuket-local-bus.htm</string>
    <string name="hotel1_name">Amari Phuket</string>
    <string name="hotel1_desc">Tripadvisor reviews placed Amari Phuket as one of the highest rated in Patong and i was keen to see why. I was not disappointed!</string>
    <string name="hotel1_url">https://www.amari.com/phuket/</string>
    <string name="hotel2_name">Patong Mansion Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel2_desc">The room are clean and the bed are just right to have a good night sleep .Morning breakfast includes egg , breads, juices, and cakes. Once you walk down the street on corner of the hotel, there is a 7 Eleven at the corner just 50 m is a BBQ buffet.</string>
    <string name="hotel2_url">http://patong-mansion-hotel.business.site/</string>
    <string name="hotel3_name">Holiday Inn Resort Phuket</string>
    <string name="hotel3_desc">Holiday Inn Resort Phuket is an oasis in the middle of Patong and is within walking distance to shopping, restaurants and night life and just steps away from the beach. 10 minutes away from Jungeceylon shopping center, Soi Bangla Nightlife, and Patong beach is just across the road....</string>
    <string name="hotel3_url">https://www.ihg.com/holidayinnresorts/hotels/us/en/phuket/phuth/hoteldetail</string>
    <string name="hotel4_name">Burasari Resort</string>
    <string name="hotel4_desc">Boutique hotel in the heart of Patong</string>
    <string name="hotel4_url">http://burasari-patong.business.site/</string>
    <string name="hotel5_name">Grand Mercure Phuket Patong</string>
    <string name="hotel5_desc">The location is very close to a lot of great things to do within walking distance. The rooms are nice and bed was comfy. The service was outstanding! They went above and beyond!</string>
    <string name="hotel5_url">http://www.grandmercurephuketpatong.com/</string>
    <string name="hotel6_name">Avista Hideaway Phuket Patong</string>
    <string name="hotel6_desc">High on a lush Patong hilltop in southwestern Phuket, overlooking two magnificent bays, sits Avista Hideaway MGallery. This 5-star boutique hotel, reminiscent of a traditional Thai village, flows like water over different levels of the hillside.</string>
    <string name="hotel6_url">http://www.avista-hideaway-phuket-patong.com/</string>
    <string name="hotel7_name">Seaview Patong Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel7_desc">The glistening Andaman Sea and sandy shores of Patong Beach are just 5 meters away from our family resort in Phuket. Experience one of the most vibrant holiday destinations in Asia staying at Seaview Patong Hotel, perched at the edge of town where the beach is uncrowded and the ambiance is chilled.</string>
    <string name="hotel7_url">http://www.seaviewphuket.com/</string>
    <string name="hotel8_name">Novotel Phuket Resort</string>
    <string name="hotel8_desc">Stayed here for a weekend in November. Got an upgrade the a deluxe Sea view. The room was pretty good, with a balcony and the view was out fo the world. The staff was warm and friendly. Although, one thing which I didn\'t like was the breakfast. We being veg had very limited options which is understandable.</string>
    <string name="hotel8_url">https://www.novotelphuket.com/</string>
</resources>
